wemakescholars.com 2016-05-15

# Best Scholarship and Internship Opportunities available globally | WMS

We recognize that your privacy is very important and will take it seriously. Hence, we strive to provide a safe, secure user experience. This Privacy Policy describes WeMakeScholars.com’s policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information. The terms "we", "us", "our", and "WeMakeScholars" refer to WeMakeScholars Inc., incorporated in India. The terms “Site”, “this website” refers to “wemakescholars.com”.

#### Disclaimer

Wemakescholars reserves the right to change privacy policy of the site, at any time and in its sole discretion. Any changes will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes will constitute your acceptance of such changes. We encourage you to review the Site Privacy Policy whenever you visit this website. 

While this Privacy Policy states our standards for maintenance of data, we will make efforts to meet them. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of data. As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of data. In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.

#### Collection of Information and use

We collect information about you when you directly submit it during signing up such as your name, email-id. If you use your Facebook, g+, or any other social networking site ("SNS") account information to sign in to WeMakeScholars.com, we will collect and store your SNS user ID. If you connect your SNS account with WeMakeScholars.com, we ask for your permission to enable posting from WeMakeScholars.com and to collect certain information from your SNS account such as information from your SNS profile.

We also collect information about you when you fill your profile and your profile picture as well. Information submitted by you in your profile, would be publicly available except few like your date of birth, pincode/postcode, email-id, mobile number and your preferences. This information might be used for the purpose of determining your potential interest in receiving email or other communications about particular products or services. Your email-id and mobile number would only be used by WeMakeScholars.com to send some notifications or promotions. You can also control receipt of few messages by changing your email notification preferences in your Settings page. We store only your current profile picture on wemakescholars.com account, your previous pictures will not be stored by us.

If you apply to become a mentor, then you may have to submit your scanned degree certificates and award letters. These certificates will not be available to the users, other mentors or anywhere else on the web; it is only for the use of Wemakescholars team. Wemakescholars puts it’s all the efforts to keep your documents safe, but in no circumstances Wemakescholars is liable for any action for unintentional loss of your documents. In addition to general user information, your information filled in “Ask me about” section and the amount you charge for the services will also be visible publicly.

In addition we may indirectly collect information about you when you use certain third party services on this website. We also gather or may gather certain information about your use of our Site, such as what areas you visit and what services you access. Moreover, there is information about your computer hardware and software that is or may be collected by us. This information can include without limitation your IP address, device type, unique device identifier, browser type, domain names, numbers of pages viewed, length of time spent, date and time and referring or exit websites. We may also capture other data, such as search criteria and results. We also use log files to build pictures of how our Site is used that help us to monitor and improve the service. We cannot identify you from your log files. As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather additional information through other methods.

Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enable us to personalise your visits to this website, simplify the signing-in procedure, keep track of your preferences and to track the usage of this Site. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored in the hard drive of your computer by your browser. Your browser will have the option to prevent websites using cookies (your browser's help screen or manual will tell you how to do this), but please note that this may reduce the functionality of this Site and other websites.

You also provide us information in the form of user content you post to the Service. Your posts, comments, and other contributions on the Service, and metadata about them (such as when you posted them), are publicly viewable on the Service, along with your name and basic information. This information may be searched by search engines and be republished elsewhere on the Web. You own complete right on the information you post on this website. But WeMakeScholars has the rights to use this content for promotional or other related purposes.

If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address and our responses.

Please remember that if you post any of your personal information in public areas of Wemakescholars, such as in discussion boards, such information may be collected and used by others over whom Wemakescholars has no control. We are not responsible for the use made by third parties of information you post or otherwise make available in public areas of this website.

If you choose to use our “Invite” option to invite a friend to the Service, we may ask you for that person's email address and automatically send an email invitation. If you use your Facebook or g+ to invite friends, we will ask for your permission to collect certain information from your SNS account such as contacts, friends, followers and we may also collect and store your SNS user ID. We use this information to send invitations, to register your friend if your invitation is accepted, to track the success of our invitation service, and to identify your friends on WeMakeScholars.com.

_Access to and correction of personal information_

Users and Mentors can access and alter their personal profiles at any time through editing option in their profile section. Users and Mentors also have rights of access to, and correction of, personal information that WeMakeScholars holds about them. Members should be aware that, as of now WeMakeScholars doesn’t allow them to delete their account from the platform.

#### Sharing of information

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, mobile number and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer or assign such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution. 

We may share or disclose your information with your consent in conditions such as if you book tickets for an event through this website. We cannot control third parties' use of your information.

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect our rights or property.

Wemakescholars may use an external Facebook Comment Box plug in provided by Facebook or any other social media account linked commenting system for users to comment on the content posted on Wemakescholars and its sub-domains. Example of this can be blog but it is not limited to just this. User can comment using their facebook or other social media profiles. Please note that this data (user profile and comment) are not stored on Wemakescholars servers and databases and we have no control over how this data is used and displayed on associated social media networks and their privacy and data usage policies. Moreover, your comments would be visible to all the users (logged in or not logged in) of this website. 

Your data may be stored and processed in or outside India (for instance, on servers or databases co- located with hosting providers). Your usage of the Site constitutes consent to this transfer of your data.

We may share the non-personally identifiable information including the information submitted by you or automatically collected, publicly in the aggregated forms for any purpose including, but not limited to, research and marketing purposes, and our use and disclosure of such information is not subject to any restrictions under this Privacy Policy.

We may allow third-party ad servers or ad networks to serve advertisements on the Service and on third- party services. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on WeMakeScholars.com. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content. WeMakeScholars does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks WeMakeScholars to show an advertisement to a certain audience and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. Our privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, third-party advertisers. Please consult the respective privacy policies of such advertisers for more information.

#### Transactional information

Any information related to the transaction you do through this website such as your card details, bank details or other secret information, are not saved by WeMakeScholars as you fill all the payment related information on your bank's site. We accept Visa and Master Credit Card, Debit Cards and Net banking as mode of payments which are processed through our payment gateway partner Avenues (India) Pvt Ltd.

#### Children

Wemakescholars is not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are over thirteen, but under the legal age of majority, your parent or legal guardian must consent to this Terms of Service and Privacy Policy, and affirm that they accept this Agreement on behalf of, and bear all legal and financial responsibility and liability for the actions of, any child between the age of 13 and majority, and expressly ratify and confirm any acts of any such child and all users of the account. 

#### Job Applicants

If your information is submitted to us through our Service when applying for a position with our company, the information will be used to consider your application. We may retain your information for any period of time. This information may be shared with other companies for the purpose of evaluating your qualifications for the particular position or other available positions, as well as with third-party service providers retained by us to collect, maintain and analyze candidate submissions for job postings.

#### Opt-in policys

Wemakescholars follows a double opt-in policy where after submitting your email address you need to verify it by clicking on a verification link that we would send to you over given email address. Until the email is verified, you would not receive any communication or newsletter or marketing material from us.

#### Opt-out policy

Every newsletter and promotional communication from Wemakescholars contains an 'edit email preferences' link that you can click to change what do you want to receive from us on your email.

#### Links to other websites

Our Site may contain links to other website over which we have no control and we are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other websites to which you choose to link from this website. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other websites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information. This Privacy Statement applies solely to the information we collect on Wemakescholars.com and not to information collected otherwise.

#### Jurisdiction

Any dispute or issues arising out of any activity regarding the use of this website will be governed by the laws of India and subject to exclusive jurisdiction of courts in the State of Telangana.

#### Contact Information

If you have any questions about our cancellation and refund policy or our Site as a whole, please feel free to contact us at  hello@wemakescholars.com
